<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Discover – Blog</title>
    <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Project Discover</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog: Januar 2022 release</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2022/01/31/januar-2022-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2022/01/31/januar-2022-release/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;What’s new in the January 2022 release of Project Discover™ ?
This release contains the following new features&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process documentation: available to TIBCO Cloud Nimbus customers, you can now generate a Nimbus map to document the discovered variants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Filter panel overlay enhancement: you now have the ability to Filter In/Out on both Events/Cases. Also, the filter dialog can now be maximized for better usability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new visualization is added to several pages of the Spotfire templates: the &amp;lsquo;icicle&amp;rsquo; mod allows to dynamically navigate the data associated with events. You can use it both for filtering and navigation purpose. Think about it as a sort of combination of a tree map and a cross table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We added documentation to the preview Spotfire DXP, allowing to define filters as pre-processing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bug fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;keep your feedbacks coming!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog: October 2021 release</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2021/11/01/october-2021-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2021/11/01/october-2021-release/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;What’s new in the October 2021 release Project Discover™ ?
This release contains the following new features&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysis KPI Overview: Quickly visualize an overview of the key metrics without having to open analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysis Compare: Quickly measure improvements from one analysis (before) to the other (after). Up to 3 simultaneous comparisons&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to Filter from the process graph, using a new contextual menu. Allowing more interactions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to Visually group activities using an attribute. Allowing to simplify the process graph to better understand it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some pre-processing filters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated templates and Spotfire report templates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bug fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;keep your feedbacks coming!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog: September 2021 release</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2021/09/23/september-2021-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2021/09/23/september-2021-release/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;What’s new in the September 2021 release Project Discover?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This major release contains:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;File Screen&lt;/b&gt; improved usability. Part of the Datasets tab, this new screen allows to Upload, Browse and Delete CSV files separately from the new Dataset wizard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Details on Datasets&lt;/b&gt; allows to see meta-data information about Datasets at a glance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Language Review&lt;/b&gt; some terms have been improved for better user experience and ease of use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;major Angular 12 Update&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Performance Improvements&lt;/b&gt; when loading dashboards and importing data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;keep your feedbacks coming!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog: July 2021 release</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2021/07/14/july-2021-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2021/07/14/july-2021-release/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;What’s new in the July 2021 release Project Discover?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This minor release contains:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Filter Feature&lt;/b&gt; Adds advanced Filter features to all Analysis. Filter overlay can be configured to be shown side by side with the process mining results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Advanced Auto-Mapper&lt;/b&gt; reworked Auto-Mapper Features, to improve Data preparation when importing new Event Data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Auto-Mapper Setting&lt;/b&gt; new Options in Auto-Mapper Setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spotfire Template&lt;/b&gt; new advanced Spotfire Configurations Settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Security Updates&lt;/b&gt; 3rd Party Component updates because of Security Issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;with the next release we move to Angular 12, also to gain some more performance advantages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog: June 2021 release</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2021/06/14/june-2021-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2021/06/14/june-2021-release/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;What’s new in the June 2021 release Project Discover?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This release is a major release that contains both architectural enhancements and new process mining features in the Process Control Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Architecture:&lt;/b&gt; Simplified, Cloud Native and API led, we now support a multi-tenant database, a setup that could be particularly interesting for partners that may want to offer TIBCO Process mining solution as a service to their customers. We also upgraded to the latest versions of Spark and included various performance improvements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Datasets:&lt;/b&gt; We simplified the way customers can bring their event logs data coming from their operational systems. Datasets are now managed independently from process analysis and the same dataset can now be reused in multiple process analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Connectors:&lt;/b&gt; TIBCO Data virtualisation is now fully part of the solution and brings a wide range of data source connectivity for databases, files, big data, cloud sources, packaged applications, and more. Overall this represents around 350+ connectors and there’s also a kit for building your custom adapter if needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Templates:&lt;/b&gt; You can now fully customize the visual analytics reports, using the full power of TIBCO Cloud Spotfire. Templates will help you associate those reports to your process analysis, customize the navigation menu, and share with your different users. The extensibility options given by templates are limitless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Investigations:&lt;/b&gt; You can now design your own investigation (case management style) apps in Live Apps and bring them into the Process Control Center with a new visual configurator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Visual Analytics:&lt;/b&gt; Two templates are now provided: one for previewing your datasets during the process analysis configuration, and one for visualizing the process mining results. We introduced important improvements, including using the new Spotfire Mods feature for various visualisations including the process graph.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;more soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog: Nov. 2020 release</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2020/11/06/nov.-2020-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2020/11/06/nov.-2020-release/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;new Features added:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added progress bar to Process Analysis allowing to track the progress of process mining computation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added automatic guessing of date formats when creating new analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;new contextual Online Help&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;updated Documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;more soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog: TIBCO NOW update</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2020/09/23/tibco-now-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2020/09/23/tibco-now-update/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Project Discover is mentioned many times on Center Stage of TIBCO NOW 2020.
Join our Demo Booth &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;increased-business-value-with-augmented-operational-insight&#34;&gt;Increased Business Value with Augmented Operational Insight&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you know how your business processes are performing? Are you aware of any inefficiencies or resource constraints? Are you compliant and meeting regulatory needs? Join this session to learn how Project Discover process mining by TIBCO LABS can answer these questions and more. Learn how to use event logs and powerful visual analytics to discover, re-engineer, and continuously monitor your business processes at scale. Predict future behaviors for smarter processes and see how to refactor your business for increased agility and performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2020.now.tibco.com/sessions/increased-business-value-with-augmented-operational-insight&#34;&gt;TIBCO NOW 2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, we announced that our Source will be available soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog: July 2020 release</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2020/07/14/july-2020-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2020/07/14/july-2020-release/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;new Features added:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;reworked Analytics Dashboards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;new File Importer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;new Configuration and Settings Dialogs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;new Investigation Case Types: Compliance &amp;amp; Improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;updated Process Analysis Life-Cycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;reworked UX Designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;more soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog: project Updates</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2020/05/03/project-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2020/05/03/project-updates/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;We are proud to have the first Process Mining Reference Story on our Site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference Story on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tibco.com/customers/invitalia&#34;&gt;TIBCO Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference Video on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rjsOf7hZbs8&#34;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Process Mining Webinar &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tibco.com/resources/demand-webinar/invitalia-implements-process-mining-boost-economic-growth&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Official &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tibco.com/solutions/process-mining-solutions&#34;&gt;TIBCO Process Mining Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;looking forward having more great updates soon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog: Initial Release</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2020/01/09/initial-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/labs-discover/blog/2020/01/09/initial-release/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;We started the process of releasing the first public Implementation of the TIBCO LABS™ Process-Mining Solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The LABS Project is working closely with early customers to explore their needs and requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;expect a lot unique features from the release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
